He's not following me... Okay!
I can't even eat my lunch in peace.
Every free second I get,
it's like he's right there.
Damn it! The cut from my kidney
transplant only just closed up.
My stomach and stress are killing me.
He's seriously got some nerve to
be able to tell the same chick
he told to go sell her body
that he loves her.
And...
He's always smiling, so it's impossible
to tell what he's thinking.
Yoshino!
H-How'd you find me here?!
I think it's my love for you.
No matter where you are, I instantly know.
What?!
I'm kidding. Though I'm serious
about the fact that I love you.
Uh, could you seriously stop with that?
Sorry, my bad. The real
answer's inside your bag.
Your electronic dictionary...
I crammed a GPS module in there.
What?!
Man, it's great knowing exactly
where you are so quickly.
God damn it!
Hey, you!
You tryin' to pick a fight with me?!
The idea was to confess before
you found out and got mad...
Did you get mad anyway?
If this don't look mad to you, better trade
in yer eyeballs at the optometrist!
I admit to installing the GPS, but I actually
had something I needed to tell you.
We've actually gotta be at the house tonight,
together, without going anywhere.
The old man has something
to discuss with us, apparently.
Let Me Express My Sincerity, and Maybe Earn
Your Affection in the Process
What's this supposed to be about?
A few too many things come to mind...
Organ
Selling
Classmates
Bullying
It's not going to be a big deal. Relax.
Do you know something?
Huh? Where's the boss?
The boss has business that
he can't get away from.
So I'm handling this instead.
Yoshino, I think this is your
first time meeting them...
This is Tachibana-san and Inamori-san.
Hey there.
I know how he looks,
but Tachibana-san's a good guy.
You wanna die, you little shit?
I'm only saying this once,
so stay quiet and listen.
That goes double for you, girl.
This is recent news, but the daughter of
Akaza Enterprises's president has gone missing.
A-Akaza Enterprises...?
A third-string Tokusa Clan affiliate.
Tokusa Clan
1st Tier
(Main Family)
2nd Tier Groups
(Miyama Family etc.)
3rd Tier Groups
(Akaza Enterprises etc.)
4th Tier Groups
Et cetera
Basically, third from the top.
As I'm sure you're aware,
we're second from the top.
This girl was roughly the
same age as you two.
Maybe she just ran away from home,
or maybe someone grabbed her.
Which wouldn't normally be a
big deal, except right now,
we've got a similar girl on our hands.
If anything happens, there'll be
hell to pay. Somei Yoshino.
Y-Yes?
For now, until President Akaza's
daughter has been found,
you need to be with Kirishima 24 hours a day.
And if that's no good, make use of Inamori.
Understood?
Got it.
Good to have you.
Aw, crap.
Twenty-four hours a day with him?
Even odds are I snap and kill this dude.
Yoshino? Something wrong?
N-No, not really.
I guess I'm going to have to stay
inside the house for a while.
What? Why?
I actually made reservations so
we could go out and have dinner.
Did you listen to a single thing they—
You worry too much, Yoshino.
That's part of your charm, though.
I really doubt this has anything
to do with us, in any case.
Do you know something about it?
How about you join me for dinner,
and I spill the beans?
I let him talk me into it.
What am I looking at here?
It's deep-fried hasu.
H-Hasu...?
It's lotus root.
Lotus?
They call lotus "hasu"?
Sounds kinda Tokyo-y.
It's good. Has a soy-sauce flavor to it.
Wh-What is it?
Was just thinking how cute you are.
Look, given the situation...
What exactly about me do you like?
What do you mean?
Well, if you honestly think there's
any chance I could fall for you,
you probably have flowers growing
where you oughta have brain cells.
You're right! I love everything about you,
but I especially love how
you say stuff like that.
You can have mine, too.
I don't get it...
He's being as polite as possible,
but it sure doesn't feel
any less threatening.
If anything...
And actually...
Virgin
No one has ever said they liked me before,
so I've got no basis for comparison!
Oh, I just remembered my promise.
Here's what's up with President
Akazawa's missing daughter.
Akazawa Shiori, 20 years old.
Attends a junior college in Kanagawa.
Her arm... Are those real tattoos?
Yeah, maybe not the smartest move.
But she's got no police record.
I had chat with her two years ago, at the
funeral for a consultant to the main family.
She was a pretty typical spoiled rich girl.
You really don't know where she's gone?
Well, she either ran away
or got snatched by some punk and sold off
for a couple of hundred thousand yen.
My money's on one of those two.
That ain't funny.
Especially considering the
situation you and I are in.
The same thing could happen
to us, you realize?
Oh, I'll be fine.
Unlike with you and your grandfather,
I'm not Patriarch Miyama's grandson by blood.
He decided not to have any kids,
meaning no grandkids either.
He's actually my grandfather's older
brother—my granduncle, basically.
But when I was twelve, I imposed on him.
You... imposed?
You wanted to become a yakuza?
Of course not. He was just where I ended up
at the end of my line of options.
Sorry. I gotta get this.
At twelve years old...?
How the hell does a kid like that end up
making himself at home with the yakuza?
You done already?
Yeah, the thing is, they found one
of Akaza Enterprises's guys dead.
Something's afoot.
The body belonged to an associate
member of Akazaka Enterprises.
He started out as a host and ended up running
a handful of restaurants around the city.
Can I point something out?
You're sitting there like you belong,
but that's not your desk!
You're not even in this class!
Anyway, turns out he was running
some underground gambling.
Are you listening, man?
In particular, he was running gaming rooms.
Rooms...?
The idea is, you rent out some apartments,
and leave out baccarat tables
or whatever for people to use.
And it seems our Akaza girl was
a regular at one of those rooms.
Our stiff and Akaza Shiori
used to gamble together,
and she was how he got the
introduction into the family.
How do you know all of this?
You wanna know?
Are you gonna tell me if I say yes?
Nope!
Then how 'bout I strangle you instead?!
Look, I'm pretty much ignorant to what
goes on outside of Tokusa Clan turf.
Huh? Turf...?
C'mon, it's like...
When you're walking around town,
from this street and beyond
is this group's turf,
while in the other direction,
it belongs to a different family.
Never really thought about it before.
Well, your guys pretty much
run Osaka, after all.
Territorial Quagmire
Ishiro Clan
Tokusa Clan
Katabami Clan
But in Tokyo, about seventy percent
belongs to the Tokusa Clan,
with the rest belonging to other people.
And it's been a hundred-year bloody
stalemate between us and the other guys!
You think that's funny?
I really hate to ask you
to help me out like this!
I forgot that the power frequency
between Tokyo and Osaka was different,
and I brought a really ancient
hairdryer with me...
No, if anything we should've had
appliances prepared for you. I'm sorry.
He's the first normal, nice person
I've met in Tokyo!
Kirishima-san was disappointed he wasn't
able to join us because of the sudden funeral.
You and he seem to get along.
Not at all!
To be honest, I don't understand
most of what he says.
Well, if we're being honest,
I don't think I've ever had a
proper conversation with him.
Really?
When I first met him, Kirishima-san
was still in middle school...
but he sure didn't seem like it.
And it's never gotten any
easier to talk to him.
Come to think of it,
he said that he imposed on the Miyama
Family when he was twelve years old...
Is that true?
This is just what I was told,
but Kirishima-san caused a pretty major
violent incident when he was in fifth grade.
It was a big enough deal that his parents
weren't able to handle it on their own,
so the boss took care of it, and that's
how he ended up with the family.
Wh-When you say violent...
There were 20 other kids altogether,
both classmates and older students.
Snapped bones all around.
Snapped bones?!
Er, I mean, this is all just hearsay,
so who knows, really!
Sorry, I shouldn't have mentioned it.
Just forget I said anything.
Ugh, traffic is so bad
around this time of day.
Huh?
Akaza Shiori, 20 years old.
I-Is that Akaza...
Shiori?
Hello. What's up? Rare of you to call me.
Did you get your new hairdryer?
Yeah, I did. Can you talk right now?
You see, uh... I think I just saw a girl
resembling President Akaza's daughter.
She had the same tattoo.
Looks like her being "missing"
was a load of crap.
On top of that, her old man's
been hard to track down lately.
I bet they're both trying to lay low.
They're both hiding?
Why would they do something like that?
More importantly, do you
know where you saw her?
Oh, I see. Nox Tokyo.
She just had to make it awkward...
It's a pretty famous club, right?
How's it awkward?
It's not on our turf.
It belongs to the Kirigaya-gumi.
Wait, Kirigaya-gumi?!
That's one of my family's!
Yep. Which means our guys wouldn't
be seen wandering around there.
Pretty clever trick, really.
I'm not technically with the family,
so I could go...
Wait, are you going to?!
Well, yeah.
How about you don't?!
I might be totally wrong, and besides,
why would you need to handle it?
It's fine. Don't worry.
Clubs don't let people bring in the real
dangerous stuff, so I doubt I'll die.
Do you not understand the concept
of avoiding danger in general?
Fine. I'm gonna put in a call to the
family office about wanting to drop by.
They'll probably let us both in if it's a
request from Boss Somei's granddaughter.
What's gotten into you, Yoshino?
If you wanted to party,
I could've shown you to—
It's my fault for telling you
in the first place!
I'll see you there. Later.
This could end up complicating
things for that one deal.
Should me and a few of the
younger guys go with him?
Leave it.
If he screws up, then he
just has to take responsibility for it.
And if he dies, then he dies.
Too loud! What the hell?!
Damn it, I would've been happy going my whole
life without stepping into a place like this!
Wh-What the hell?! Their parents would cry
if they saw 'em doing that!
You're not gonna see a lot
of families around here.
It's dangerous, Yoshino,
so stick close to me, okay?
Shiori, you're going
overseas tomorrow, right?
Should you be drinking in here?
I'm not even gonna be able to
come back to Japan for a while.
My dad worries too much,
and it's so obnoxious.
I'm fed up with having people
watch me all the time!
What did you even do, Shiori?
She was cheating at the baccarat
tables with the dead guy.
Against the Filipino mafia, of all people.
The mafia?! Yikes!
You took them for 500 mill.
How stupid are you?
You saw what happened
to the other guy, right?
That's why I paid you guys for protection, duh.
All I even did was invite those
rich old dudes to gamble.
The cheating wasn't me.
Five hundred mill, huh?
Sounds like you had a lot of fun.
Good to see you again, Akaza Shiori-san.
Wh-Who are you?
Aw, you don't remember me?
We met at Captain Kashiwagi's funeral.
I'm Miyama Gaku's grandson,
Miyama Kirishima.
H-Hi there. I'm Somei.
Huh? Miyama?
Hey, Shiori, do you seriously know this guy?
N-Never seen him in my life.
Look, I don't know who sent you here,
but do you think can kill me on your own?
Are you crazy? I've got no reason
to kill you in the first place.
The only people who do are probably
the Filipino mob, right?
Makes me wonder where
President Akaza ran off to.
He's gotta be terrified...
What with his daughter ripping off a Filipino
crime syndicate for a cool half billion.
What are you getting at?
How about you cancel your overseas trip
tomorrow and join me at our office instead?
Say what?
If you and your father keep this up,
it's gonna get past the point of no return.
I'm sure you realize the trouble you're
causing for the main family, right?
President Akaza made the
right move going to ground,
but at this rate, he's gonna find himself
stuck between a rock and a hard place.
Yoshino!
Move.
Hey, you assholes,
what the hell am I looking at?
Is this some kinda social club?
We were just waiting for you to show up!
Shut up. All this for one punk kid.
Let's take care of it already.
Screw you! We might let
you off this time, but—
You son of a—
What the hell did you say?
Something about letting someone off?
Yeah, no, none of you are
getting out of here alive.
Who the hell—
Ow!
You little punk!
Damn, that friggin' hurts!
There were 20 other kids altogether,
both classmates and older students.
Snapped bones all around.
Well, I buy it. This guy's more than capable!
How can he hit someone with
all his strength like that?
How is he so strong?
No!
I'm just weak.
And I ain't gonna back down
in this mess, damn it!
Damn it! You son of a—
Die, asshole!
You bi—
What the hell are you
screaming for, dumbass?
No one wants to hear it! How about you die?!
Shit, I broke the hairdryer.
It ain't foldin' anymore...
Yoshino, you're bleeding!
It's just a bloody nose.
I should mention you've got
somethin' stuck in yer leg.
Hey, wake up. You don't get to sleep,
not after making Yoshino bleed.
Uh, he ain't hearin' anythin' now.
Kill you... I'll kill... dead.
Aw, but I hit him twice.
You're not killing anyone.
You made my girl bleed, asshole.
You don't even get to die, yet.
I want another ten liters of blood
from you before I'm satisfied.
Knock it off! What's yer problem?
What kinda maniac kills somebody
over a single hit, huh?!
But you told him to die before...
Killin' off trash like this
ain't even worth it!
But you're bleeding.
This ain't from when I got hit.
I fell and landed on my face.
That's such a lie.
No, it ain't! And wait,
where'd Akaza Shiori go?!
Sh-She ain't dead... right?
Who cares if she is?
I'm too depressed to care.
Well, get a grip, damn it!
I guess President Akaza got away
with just being expelled.
News Updates
Yakuza Families
Organized Crime News
More like exiled.
His daughter isn't safe in Japan,
so she ended up heading overseas, too.
I've gotta ask...
You seem more injured than I remember.
Well, I made a bunch of trouble on
Kirigaya-gumi turf, so I got a talking-to.
What's that?
Ten million yen.
What did you do this time...?
This is my cut of the 500 mill, as split
between the Filipino mafia and my family.
In exchange for finding the girl
and President Akaza,
they decided to split the money
down the middle and call it a day.
And I found them,
so I get ten million to myself.
Which is now yours, Yoshino.
Whoa, no way! I can't take this!
There's no reason for me to!
You literally gave me four mill the other day.
I was thinking about selling
a kidney to pay you back,
but I didn't really have the right hookup...
And I don't really know how to show that
I'm being sincere other than with cash.
You're talkin' about sincerity, but there's
a lotta other stuff we gotta address here.
I guess I could sell my corneas, then?
That'll only be 100 thou,
but I know the right people.
This is ridiculous.
I don't need the money, or your corneas.
What I need is a new hairdryer,
and you need to come along.
Since I broke the other.
Of course!
Where should we go after
picking up the hairdryer?
How about a movie?
Naw, after we buy it, I'm goin' straight home.